BE:

app − This directory contains the core code of the application.

bootstrap − This directory contains the application bootstrapping script.

config − This directory contains configuration files of application.

database − This folder contains your database migration and seeds.

public − This is the application’s document root. It starts the Laravel application. 
It also contains the assets of the application like JavaScript, CSS, Images, etc.

resources − This directory contains raw assets such as the LESS & Sass files, 
localization and language files, and Templates that are rendered as HTML.

storage − This directory contains App storage, like file uploads etc. 
Framework storage (cache), and application-generated logs.

test − This directory contains various test cases.

vendor − This directory contains composer dependencies.

app-subfolder:
Console − All the artisan commands are stored in this directory.

Events − This directory stores events that your application can raise. 
Events may be used to alert other parts of your application that a given action has occurred, 
providing a great deal of flexibility and decoupling.

Exceptions − This directory contains your application's exception handler and is also a good 
place to stick any exceptions thrown by your application.

Http − This directory contains your controllers, filters, and requests.

Jobs − This directory contains the queueable jobs for your application.

Listeners − This directory contains the handler classes for your events. Handlers receive an 
event and perform logic in response to the event being fired. For example, a UserRegistered 
event might be handled by a SendWelcomeEmail listener.

Policies − This directory contains various policies of the application

Providers − This directory contains various service providers.

FE:
